ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Records 5780/207
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- SFK, customer, Logan Drive, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- SFK, customer, Macy's, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- SFK, customer, Marcasiano, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- SFK, customer, N.E. Wear, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- SFK, customer, Nordstrom, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- SFK, customer, One 212, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- SFK, customer, Pamela Morris, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- SFK, customer, Ross, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- SFK, customer, Saks, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- SFK, customer, Susan Barry, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- SFK, customer, Timberland, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- SFK, customer, Tommy Hilfiger, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Dun and Bradstreet Ratings, various companies, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- SFK, equipment, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- SFK, Edgar Romney, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- SFK, Frabicas Tejedoras, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- SFK, Hampshire Group, Ltd., 1994 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- SFK, Huelgainotas (Agustin Ramirez), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- SFK, Huelgainotas (Agustin Ramirez), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- SFK, Huelgainotas (Agustin Ramirez), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- SFK, Inteligencia a David (Young), December 1, 1994 and February 3, 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- SFK, Inteligencia a David Young, December 13, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- SFK, Inteligencia a David Young, November 21, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- SFK, Inteligencia a David Young, March 1,7,14, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- SFK, Inteligencia a Brent Garren, March 9, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- SFK, Juntas, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- SFK, Juntas generales, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- SFK, Jack Yacobian, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- SFK, lista de Trabajadores, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- SFK, Lou Wenisch, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- SFK, lista de clientes, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Misc., 1974-1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- SFK, orders, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- SFK, personal, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- SFK, Pendleton, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- SFK, production reports, misc., 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- SFK, yarn, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- SFK, draft settlement agreement, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- SFK, strike support, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- SFK, sales by customer, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- SFK, lu house, correspondence, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- SFK, sample yarn, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- SFK, style #5, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- SFK, Tom Lantos, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- SFK, Traducciones, Sonia, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- SFK, Tarjetas Firmadas, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- SFK, trucking, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- SFK, varios, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- SFK, Volante para venta en Diciembre, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- SFK, Volante, February 6 and March 21, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 30)